localcircles.com 2015-12-28

# LocalCircles - Social Media for Communities, Governance and Urban Daily Life

Welcome to LocalCircles. By signing up at LocalCircles.com, you agree to this Privacy Policy, which is part of your Membership Agreement at LocalCircles. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at [support@localcircles.com](mailto:support@LocalCircles.com).

### Information We receive about you:

We receive the following types of information about you:

### Your Registration Information.

When you sign up for the site, you are required to provide your gender, name, email address, password, and approximate location of where you live at signup.

### Information You Share to Create or Join a Circle.

Joining an Interest Circle requires you to share your location. Joining a Neighborhood Circle requires that you share your address, building/apartment number, how long you have been living in that house/apartment, and optionally, if you hold an official position. Joining a School Circle requires you to enter information about your child that goes to that school. Joining a Work Circle requires you to provide your title at work, the company or group that you work in, and your expertise. We provide you with options for hiding some of your profile information. However, to ensure authenticity to the Circle members, some of the fields such as your name in all types of Circles, your address in a Neighborhood Circle, your child’s information in a School Circle, your title and company in a Work Circle cannot be hidden and is visible to all the Circle members in that Circle.

### Information You Choose to Share.

Information you choose to share in your Circles on LocalCircles could be your picture, family pictures, family information, work information, phone number, interests, posts, resources, classifieds, events, ratings, reviews, and entities submitted by you etc. In some cases, we may limit your ability to edit or remove your or any other content from LocalCircles.

### Information We Automatically Collect.

Our systems automatically collect a variety of information about our users such as server logs, cookies, web sessions, your computer’s or mobile’s operating system, IP address, browser type, URLs your come from and go to, your location etc. We use this information to debug, analyze, resolve systemic problem. We also use this information to improve your experience of our service and notify you of relevant offers that could be of use to you. 

### Information We Receive from Others or Third-Parties.

Our users are allowed to invite other members that they believe belong should get access to a particular circle. If they choose to invite you with your email address, we retain that email address and send you an invitation from that Circle member. We may also send you occasional reminders to join the Circles that you were invited to. Sometimes, to start a location-based Circle, we may work with neighborhoods, schools, work places, or interest clubs, Government authorities, partners who want to build a circle or in some cases we may obtain your information directly from the public domain. In some of these cases, your information may not come from you or one of your associates. If you are not a member and would like us to delete your non-public information, please contact us at [support@localcircles.com](mailto:support@LocalCircles.com).

### Notifications and Other Messages:

We may send you notifications and other messages using the contact information we have for you, like your email address or your phone number. We will alert you of various activities within your Circles via email. You can manage your email preferences on the settings page at LocalCircles.com. Certain member-related administrative email can only be turned off by terminating your account. 

### Personal Information:

We allow you to create a member profile, and enter your details like name, phone number, address, etc. We do not show your address to anyone other than your neighbors in your neighborhood Circle. For all the other Circle members, we only show how far you live from them.

### Third Party Service Providers:

We give your information to the people and companies that help us provide the services we offer. For example, we may use outside vendors to help host our website, serve photos and videos, process payments, or provide search results. In some cases we provide the service jointly with another company. 

In all of these cases our partners must agree to only use your information consistent with the agreement we enter into with them, as well as this privacy policy.

We may allow a potential acquirer or merger partner to review our database, although we would restrict their use and disclosure of this data during the diligence phase.

We never share your contact details with marketers so you do not receive from any third party offers/emails/SMS as a result of signing up with LocalCircles.

### Offers for Goods and Services:

In future, we may send emails you concerning goods and services we believe may be attractive to you. You may always elect not to receive these emails on the "Email Preferences" page.

In the future, we may create a section of the website to present offers for goods and services we think you would like. We will never turn over your personally identifiable information to third party marketers without your consent.

We may choose to give selective database access to certain third-party providers post a non-disclosure agreement with them.

### Affiliated Companies or Alliances.

LocalCircles may share your data with its parent companies, subsidiary, other joint ventures or third-party acquirers. We may also have to allow a potential merger or an acquisition partner to review our database. However, they will have limited access during the due diligence phase until a transaction has materialized. 

### Deleting your Content or Account.

You can delete your account by contacting us at support@localcircles.com from the email address you used to create your account. Deleting your account will delete the information that you provided on your profile. However, we may choose to retain the content that you had submitted to the Circles you were part of. If you leave a Circle, the information you had submitted to that Circle is also retained in that Circle. Unless there are any specific mandatory obligations to delete your data, we reserve the right to retain information in our databases and records indefinitely.

### Respecting the Privacy of Your Circles.

The local circles at LocalCircles are closed social or community networks, where members are allowed to interact among themselves. For this reason, access to information that’s available in a Circle is strictly restricted to the members of that Circle. For example, we don't let public web search engines (such as Google) index member-submitted Content in any of the local circles. For these local circles, you should not share information about one member of your Circle or information about any interactions of that member to anyone outside that Circle without taking explicit permission from that member.

LocalCircles itself operates many community circles i.e. (National, City, Cause and Governance circles are considered public circles for larger public good) and hence the activity in these circles may be shared with other social media sites, print or TV media. In most, cases these community circles are used by our members to create broader awareness about particular issues or provide feedback to Government/Organizations. For these community circles, you are welcome to share information about a member of your Circle or information about any interactions outside the circle with social media, print or TV media. You are not allowed to gather information from LocalCircles manually through posts or comments or using automated web tools. Soliciting people’s contact details for business/promotional activities is not permissible. Violating these terms may result in revocation of your account privileges including a permanent ban from our website.

### Abiding by the Law.

If compliance to law requires us to share some or all of your data at LocalCircles with Government authorities, we may disclose your data.

### Our Limitations.

LocalCircles always strives to respect the privacy of its users. However, in a complex technology environment like ours, a defect or error in our software/hardware might disclose your data in ways inconsistent with our privacy policy. In these situations, we will try to rectify the situation to the best of our ability.

### User Access and Security.

LocalCircles uses https technology and a username and password to prevent unauthorized access to your content. However, Internet by design is susceptible to a variety of security threats.

### Change of Control.

If the ownership of our business changes, we may transfer your information to the new owner so they can continue to operate the service. But they will still have to honor the commitments we have made.

### Notice of Changes:

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make changes to this policy we will notify you by publication on this page. 

### For any questions on this Privacy Policy, we encourage to contact us at:

LocalCircles.com, Inc.,  
5255 Stevens Creek Blvd, Suite 276 Santa Clara CA 95051.   
Email: [support@LocalCircles.com](mailto:support@LocalCircles.com). 

This policy was last updated on January 1st, 2015.
